[Perfect Marriage Revenge]
[This is a work of fiction. Characters, places, agencies, incidents, organizations, religion, and the setting
have no connections to real life. Child actors were filmed safely with guardian presence and agreement.]
- Aigoo, you made it.
- Chairwoman.
[Episode 4]
Thank you for coming all the way out here.
No problem. It's quiet out here, very nice.
If we meet somewhere crowded,
there will be strange rumors.
We thought a more humble
setting like this might be better.
Actually, I don't understand.
If you wanted to take in our
child as your daughter-in-law,
you wouldn't treat us like this.
- Honey, how could you be so rude?
- No.
You understand what's going on. Seems like
you're the actual big shot of the Hanwool Group.
I'm Cha Yeon Hwa.
I'm Lee Jung Hye.
Are we all here, then?
Our daughter is on her way...
There she is.
Honey.
Jae Ho, I told you not to have her drive!
Dad, please!
I'm sorry, Father...
Hello!
Our other daughter is not feeling
well today and couldn't make it.
Our eldest son is also busy with
the redevelopment project, so...
Yes.
I know Taeja Group is
taking on a big project.
Yet, you still make the time
to work on the foundation.
I've heard a lot about the
Generous Person Foundation.
You let struggling single mothers and their
children live here, help them get on their feet.
The nuns and teachers do all the hard work.
All we do is pay for it.
That is an incredible thing.
That must not be easy for a businessperson.
Foundations just bleed
money the longer you do it.
That's why I'm a total
failure as a businesswoman.
I'm learning a lot today.
Seeing how the Taeja
Group could be so humble...
and seeing you be so informal
makes me look back on myself.
Earlier, you said if we really
wanted to take in your daughter,
we wouldn't be treating you like this.
I misspoke for a moment, being
disappointed on behalf of my daughter.
But I get it.
Any prestigious family would die for their
child to be Taeja Group's daughter-in-law.
We're not that shallow.
- If they like each other, we-
- But...
you must know that our daughter is adopted.
So what?
That's not Han Yi Joo's fault, is it?
If everyone thought like
you, how great would it be?
But in reality, people
talk behind your back.
"She's adopted. That's why she's
like that. She was taught wrong."
I worked extra hard not to
hear things like that, but...
She studied art and graduated from college,
but she doesn't know how to do anything yet.
She hasn't sold any pieces,
and she's not good at housework.
After marrying her off, I
worry what people will say.
What the heck? Did they
show up to ruin the marriage?
- Should we do cheers?
- For what?
If you're saying that out
of true concern for us...
you don't need to worry.
Han Yi Joo is a great
person. If she wasn't,
I would not have wanted to marry her.
Yi Joo. Do you feel the same?
I'm curious if you think you're qualified
to be the Taeja Group's daughter-in-law.
You're right, Mother.
I'm inadequate.
Like you said, I'm not good enough, but...
for the occasion, I brought a gift.
Could I show it to you?
A gift? What is it?
You painted this, Yi Joo?
I feel like I've seen it before.
I copied a painting by the
famous artist Edward Boir.
You could call it...
a fake.
Actually, my mother does
some very unique charity work.
She makes exact copies of famous paintings
to hang at welfare centers or public spaces.
For people who can't easily go to a museum.
I thought maybe the Generous Person Foundation
could hang it, so I thought I'd bring it.
Oh, my, how thoughtful of you!
Aigoo, thank you so much for this!
Hey, go hang this painting somewhere.
Where would be good?
Yes, there! How about right there?
Go ahead and put it up.
Yi Joo.
Could we talk for a second?
How did you get that painting?
I know it must be strange.
You hand-delivered that piece
to the lady from Jaeil Group.
How did you...
Among the VIP clients, she is
a fan of French intimism, no?
I saw she had moved up a tier recently.
That means she purchased
a pretty expensive piece.
I told her there was an
issue during transport.
I offered to refund her
immediately, and she gave it back.
Nonsense.
It's worth one billion.
How did you pay that back?
If you don't believe me,
why don't you check with her?
Ma'am? It's Lee Jung Hye.
The piece you purchased...
Hey, CEO Lee. I got the money.
- What?
- Yi Joo is so good at her job.
I'll be back at the gallery
to see other pieces soon.
I'm shopping now, so...
I got the paperwork back, too.
Here's your signature, Mother.
Guaranteeing its authenticity.
You really want to go at it with me?
- Are you out of your mind?
- Yes.
I am.
I'm going through with this
marriage, no matter what.
- Han Yi Joo...
- And while I'm at it, I'll do it right.
Wearing the most expensive
dress at an extravagant venue,
with Yoo Ra, Mother...
Father, Grandfather, all there to bless us.
So, Mother...
wrap up the family
introduction nicely today.
Stop trying to provoke me.
It was great to meet you today.
Safe travels home.
I'll come by and visit
you soon, Chairwoman.
- I'll have things to discuss with you.
- Sounds good.
Your eyes are about to pop out. Let's go.
So, are you proud of yourself?
For acting like you wanted to
ruin your daughter's marriage?
Why are you only mad at me?
Didn't you hear that woman run her mouth?
It's Taeja Group!
Of course, they're going to act superior.
You need to think about our
company as part of the Hanwool Group!
I'm a mother before that.
- And you're Yoo Ra's father before a CEO.
- No.
I was always a CEO first.
You brought along the kid.
Honey!
Aren't you managing the gallery?
You had no idea what Han Yi Joo was doing?
I'm sorry.
Get it together.
Where are you going so late?
How was the meeting?
- Well...
- You couldn't...
break it up, huh?
We just said hello.
Nothing is moving forward-
Yoo Ra!
Yoo Ra.
This is about Seo Do Guk, huh?
I'll talk to Yi Joo about it.
She must have thought more about it, too.
Stop. You've had enough.
Do you even know what Unni was doing today?
They had a family introduction today.
Family introduction...
What?
While you're just standing around,
the marriage is right on track.
That's ridiculous.
Where is Yi Joo right now, huh?
I don't know. She could be
at a hotel or Seo Do Guk's.
A family introduction...
Se Hyeok, do you even want to get her back?
Of course.
But I don't know how...
Then help me.
What?
I'm going to take matters
into my own hands.
Grandma.
Madam Cha, why so moody?
Do Na, what did you think?
- Of what?
- The family of the girl who wants to marry Do Guk.
What did you think?
Her mom is like a more evil
version of Cinderella's stepmom.
You saw her pretending to be nice
while putting down her daughter, right?
I know!
Accusing us of not having manners?
They put down their own child
in front of us for being adopted.
- Isn't that child abuse?
- She hasn't been a child for about 20 years.
They probably treated her
like that since childhood!
Do you think they even fed her
well? That's why she's so skinny.
What? What's wrong?
My goodness, Madam Cha.
Has she stolen your heart already?
Stolen? What do you mean?
I just feel bad for her.
Pity is something you
should feel for a stray cat.
- Not a daughter-in-law.
- Mother. I don't...
Mother. I don't...
Gosh, this is all irrelevant.
We could sit here and talk
forever. Do Guk doesn't care.
He seems totally crazy about her.
What? Crazy about her?
Girl, don't talk about
your brother like that.
Has Do Na ever treated us
like older brothers anyway?
- Hey, Oppa.
- Hey, Jung Wook.
Yes, Grandmother.
Do Na, did you quit your
job? You're always home.
What? Everyone works from
home these days. Don't you know?
I guess not. I tend to
spend day and night at work.
By the way, how did it go with
the family introduction for Do Guk?
Well, the girl seems all right.
But her mom...
I don't like her.
Really? How so?
Well, she's just so-so.
Anyway, you're fine with it, right?
- We'll see.
- What? I thought you liked her.
You really connected
with that girl, didn't you?
What connection?
I saw everything.
You two were exchanging eye contact like...
What are you talking about?
If you're going to talk
nonsense, get out. Go home!
So? How did you get my aunt's blessing?
What?
I somehow knew you two would get along.
How did that picky aunt take one look
at you and agree to meet your family?
It's nothing. I just...
Let's do it. A family
introduction. With everyone.
What?
Under one condition.
Can you keep a secret from Do Guk?
Yes. Please tell me.
I'll give you six months.
Convince Do Guk to go back to Taeja Group.
Then, we'll accept you.
If you can't, I hope you walk
away on your own, Han Yi Joo.
Will that be difficult?
No. I'll do as you say.
Do you think Seo Do Guk might
want to go back to Taeja Group?
Why? Is there talk?
No, I'm just curious.
That probably won't happen.
His grandmother chose him first as a successor,
but he left to start his own company.
He wouldn't come back, at
least for Jung Wook's sake.
Jung Wook?
You mean Do Guk's older brother?
Oh, yeah.
What? Are they not on good terms?
I mean, I don't really know about that.
Too hot!
Excuse me, can I get some ice water?
Coming!
This is way too hot.
We don't really have a
house party culture in Korea.
Unless you're really close, you
don't really go to someone's home.
So, approaches like our "online
homes" have been more popular.
That's why I'm saying let's go to
Japan first since they're similar.
I know it is, but...
going abroad creates
issues for hiring, supply...
It's something we need
to confront eventually.
There will never be a "perfect
time" to start something.
We should get ahead when it feels early.
Shouldn't you be working on the
Taeja Constructions project first?
Of course.
But is that all I should be doing?
Not prepare for the next one?
Of course, we should. But
through discussion and agreement.
We can't just start a project just
because you want to, CEO Seo.
We're not a mom-and-pop shop.
Mr. Yoo, those were some strong words...
If I can't run my company the way I want,
why should I be the CEO?
I'd rather run a mom-and-pop shop.
CEO Seo, that'd be pulling too much weight.
So...
are you doubting your employees' judgment?
Yeah, especially yours, Mr. Yoo.
You can't even tell if she's
a good woman or not...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Deputy CEO, I have
something urgent to tell you.
What? Now?
Yes, let's step outside and talk.
- Let's get some kimchi stew.
- K-Kimchi stew?
Stop making excuses about work
and say what you want to say, Mr. Yoo.
CEO Seo, I've worked for you for the
past five years, always doing my best.
And now you lust over
your subordinate's fiancée.
Don't you think you've gone too far?
I'm pretty sure I got there
after you were dumped, Mr. Yoo.
No. Yi Joo and I were taking
a break to think about things.
Yi Joo thought about it
and made her decision.
She wants to marry me.
She doesn't mean it.
Did you really know her that well?
I know how much and
how long Yi Joo liked me.
I know how upset she is, so I'm trying
to understand where she's coming from.
I'm sorry that you're being used, CEO Seo.
I don't care.
What?
I'm so in love that I will gladly be used.
I despise her pretty name
coming out of another man's mouth.
I could rip out your tongue right now.
That's love, right?
CEO Seo, what are you
going to do to Yi Joo?
What do you mean? I'll do
my duty as her life partner.
Love her, trust her, stand by her side.
So that she can do what
she truly wants to do.
You'll refund all of them?
All the fake pieces that Yi Joo made?
Say there was an issue while
tracking the ownership history.
Refund everything exactly
and get the pieces back.
Wipe the transaction history clean.
For the costs...
use the Malaysia account.
Did someone notice?
No one called the gallery...
All the authenticators
said they were perfect, too.
Do what I tell you to. Don't argue with me.
Yes, CEO Lee.
And the madam from Jaeil Group is here.
Hello, Ma'am.
Hi, CEO Lee.
I apologize for causing concern recently.
Oh, it's all right. It happens.
Were there any issues with the refund?
Of course not. She actually asked
me first if I had a non-taxable account.
I was surprised she offered
to send it there directly.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Thanks to that, I got
every single penny back.
Ma'am, I need a little favor.
I think the Hanwool employee used a
different account than the gallery uses.
Could you check for me who the sender was?
Of course.
[Seo Do Guk]
- Hello?
- What are you doing?
How about you? What are you doing?
I'm at work. I think I'm
pulling an all-nighter.
Or I might go to a hotel at dawn.
Why don't you go home?
I like hotels.
Want to come, Han Yi Joo?
I'm busy. I'm packing.
You're moving out today?
Want a ride?
No thanks, I'll call a taxi.
Don't do it alone.
What?
I'll always be by your side.
You don't have to try
to do everything alone.
Don't treat me like a kid.
If something actually difficult
comes up, I'll let you know.
I'm proud of you, Yi Joo.
You said you were busy.
Sounds like you're bored.
No, I need to work hard to feed Han Yi Joo.
Then, work harder.
Bye.
Typical.
What are you doing?
You're going to CEO
Seo's, right? I'll drive you.
No thanks, I'll go.
I know the way. I need to talk to you, too.
I said no. Se Hyeok, what are you doing?
Please let me do this.
It might be the last time.
- I'll put them inside.
- No thanks.
- Please leave.
- Yi Joo.
- Did you only think of me as your lover?
- What?
So if that part of our relationship
is over, we're strangers?
We were childhood friends who had no
one but each other in our neighborhood.
Are you blaming me right now?
- Don't you get how we got here?
- I know it was my fault.
That's why I can't be mad that you're
marrying another man right away.
Even if...
Even if this is it for us, I
will wish you happiness.
As your friend who cares about you.
What is it that you want to say?
I wouldn't be like this
for any other guy. But...
Seo Do Guk is not it.
He just met you, and now he's
proposing, meeting your family...
and having you move in?
The people who know Seo Do Guk would
never believe this. That it's nonsense.
That must be how passionate he is for me.
- What?
- When men are in love, they can't see anything else.
Like you, wanting to be close to the one you
love, you were going to marry her sister.
Am I wrong?
I...
I asked him...
if he knew my relationship with you.
I said we were friends and lovers for 20
years in our neighborhood, and he didn't care.
He doesn't want to know.
Is that something a man in love would say?
Seo Do Guk is cool about it.
Unlike pathetic you-know-who.
That's not being cool. It's apathy.
Yi Joo. I'm not just
doing this for no reason.
Seo Do Guk is a scary person.
For sure, he has some ulterior motive.
Do you know that CEO
Seo tried to kill someone?
- What?
- He pushed his own brother off a boat.
And from that incident,
his brother was disabled.
The reason CEO Seo left
Taeja Group was because
he didn't want to fight
over the successor position.
Why? Because what he
did would come to light again.
You must be in shock. I'm sorry.
Who else is going to tell you this but me?
Who else cares about you
as much as I do, Yi Joo?
So, come back to me.
And let's try again-
Get away from me.
Oppa.
You should be an actor.
Where did you hear that?
You told me yourself.
Seo Do Guk and his
brother are not on good terms.
Is it true that Seo Do Guk
pushed his brother off a boat?
- Is it?
- I don't know for sure.
It's true that Jung Wook fell over the railing
and got hurt badly while they were alone.
But it could've just been an accident.
Jung Wook said his brother pushed him.
There's a witness who
gave a similar testimony.
Anyway, no one in my
family brings that up since.
Everyone just wants to forget about it.
Do you think that's enough?
Didn't you see Han Yi Joo in shock?
She was frozen like a rock.
So they burn for each other, I see.
Just wait and see.
When the trust breaks,
they'll be on shaky ground.
[Taeja Constructions Seo Jung Wook]
[Deputy CEO Seo Jung Wook Donates
Large Sum to Disability Organization]
Sunbae!
I mean, CEO Seo! Emergency.
The Deputy CEO of Taeja Constructions...
So... Seo Jung Wook...
What did Seo Jung Wook do?
He made a mess.
Cancel? What do you mean?
You wanted to do this first.
I know.
But you're responsible, too.
- What?
- Since the news of your wedding,
there have been talks of
Hanwool and Taeja Group linking.
But Hanwool's reputation
isn't that great, you know.
The union is up in arms, saying
it ruins our building's brand.
I'll tell Grandmother myself.
I don't want her to think there's
some kind of internal division.
I have a general meeting, so...
This was decided before they
were selected as the constructors.
Why pull out now?
Did he get approval from the union members?
They're about to hold a general meeting
for the changes in the construction plan.
They'll probably write it on the
back of the agreement in fine print.
This is a huge project!
Even for Taeja Constructions,
a trillion-won project is rare.
We brought in so many companies for this.
Is there a solution, huh?
I think it'll be challenging.
It seems like a warning that they
don't wish to associate with Hanwool.
What?
Hanwool Financials is notorious
in the construction business.
They previously acquired Dongmi Constructions,
which was near bankruptcy, for over 100 billion.
Then, they embezzled the money and bankrupted
a company that could have bounced back.
So, my upcoming wedding is the issue.
It's between Han Yi Joo and me, not
between our company and Hanwool.
Taeja Constructions is even more removed.
Not so sure about that. If someone
made up a rumor in the dark,
it'll be hard to tell who
started it or how far it'll spread.
Then, we can bring it out into the light.
- Excuse me?
- What?
Why are you illegally changing the design plans?
[Noblesse Amitier Redevelopment Union Meeting]
Please rescind!
This is the agenda for today's meeting.
[Noblesse Amitier Redevelopment Union Meeting]
First, questions on the
contracted employee activity.
And the increase in construction
costs due to the change in design...
I will explain myself.
Vice President...
This is Taeja Construction's
Vice President, Seo Jung Wook.
These ladies who are hired as "advertisers"
go around knocking on senior citizens' doors,
telling them the design change
is confirmed! Isn't that illegal?
That was an unauthorized
strategy by our contractor company.
If there is an issue,
they will be responsible.
What about the change in design?
A 200-billion won increase in the
construction costs? How does that make sense?
This makes no sense!
We're going to make it make sense.
The cost didn't just randomly go up.
It's simply because we
expanded the entire site.
The benefit from that will go
right back to you, the residents.
How can you do that?
Of course, I understand
your anxieties completely.
So I, Seo Jung Wook,
promise you this one thing.
Everyone.
Isn't money what you all want the most?
In this district, we will make this complex
the most expensive property
in this country, minus Gangnam.
- I promise you.
- Now, now.
The Vice President gives you
his word. A round of applause.
But you still need to verify.
As you said earlier, it's a big project.
There can't be any mistakes.
But what I don't understand is...
the area that actually contributed to the
expansion is just the underground parking lot.
Why was the budget based
on the area above ground?
It's a trifold difference.
I think there's been a
mistake in the calculations.
Why don't you take a look
at it again? Take your time.
What happened, Manager Park?
- Yes?
- The design.
Did you upload the final version?
I-I'll look over it again with the design
team and make an announcement.
But he is...
Me?
Excuse me for a moment.
Allow me to introduce myself.
For the upcoming
reconstruction of Noblesse Amitier,
I will be collaborating with Taeja
Constructions to provide custom concepts.
I am CEO Seo Do Guk of
H-Terier, an interior design platform.
H-Terier? I've heard of it.
They're famous. I've seen them on the news.
Oh, yes. I saw them on the news.
That's right.
As VP Seo Jung Wook just said,
we cannot separate money from
the worth of an apartment building.
But another important issue is elevating
the quality of life of those who live there.
Thus, our company will work with the residents'
unique preferences and lifestyles to provide
interior concepts, supply selections, and even
floor plans to follow along and support you.
Just like how I corrected Taeja
Construction's mistake just now.
But regarding my upcoming wedding,
I hear there are talks of excluding my company
from this project due to a very private matter.
Since we're all gathered here,
could I ask for your thoughts?
As for that, when will we do the
paperwork and put it to a vote?
How about a show of hands?
Those members who wish to
create great living spaces with us,
please raise your hands.
Do Guk went all the way
over there because of him?
I see. Thanks, Secretary Jang.
First, I would like to
apologize to you, Chairwoman.
I think my wife was sad about
our first daughter getting married.
She went through a lot
while adopting our eldest.
I ask for your understanding.
No need for that.
So, what did you want to talk about today?
The new director of the
Financial Supervisory Service.
Since someone without a financial background
has been appointed, the expectations are high.
It's a big deal that someone not indebted to the
financial industry has a job dealing with money.
- But...
- But?
No one lives in this world alone.
Whether we like it or not, we all
end up owing someone something.
I imagine that's the case for him, too.
Do you remember what they
used to say in Myeongdong?
- Excuse me?
- During the day, birds listen. At night, rats listen.
If it's about money, Han Woon Jae listens.
Now that I think about it,
you're a lot like your father.
I'm not sure. Father didn't even
want me to grow the business.
Aigoo, that scared me.
Look.
[Han Woon Jae]
How did he know I was meeting his son?
Hey, what's going on?
What?
Got it. Bye.
Why would my father call you, Chairwoman?
He's so particular, you know.
He just wanted to say hello or something.
Anyway, you mean you would like my help
with Hanwool acquiring Savings Bank, right?
I knew you'd get me, Chairwoman.
Sure.
I'll think about it.
Let's eat.
Yes, Chairwoman.
How long has it been?
Maybe 30 years?
We met for the last time in
your office during the IMF.
You slapped me in the
face with a wad of cash.
I will never forget that.
It hurt so much.
You reap what you sow.
You collect that much interest.
That's why the wad had to be thick.
- You still hold a grudge against me.
- Of course!
How could I like you after all
the money you ripped off of me?
Fine.
Take this and forget about the past.
1.6 billion won.
All the interest I ever took
from you. Every single penny.
Han Woon Jae is returning
all the interest? Why?
Please take good care of my granddaughter.
She's been through so much.
She was adopted into
that home, knowing nothing.
She's had such a hard life, but...
she doesn't resent anyone.
She says she's forgiven everything.
The only thing she's
ever wanted for herself...
This marriage. I want to
make it happen for her.
So, Madam Lee, please accept my Yi Joo...
I don't want this.
- Why are you being like this?
- Look here!
This is my money.
You stole the money I earned
with my blood and sweat.
Now you're showing
off, trying to return it?
Give me a break.
I'm not showing off.
I'm giving it back to you.
I said I don't want it.
The money you touch gets
dirty. I can't even clean it.
I'll pretend I never heard
what you said. Goodbye.
Don't do this. How can I...
convey how I feel?
What is wrong with you? What are you doing!
Money is the only way I
know how to speak my heart.
Tell me how. I'll do whatever you want.
My goodness...
I'd rather die than people think I have a love
affair with an old man like you. Get out of my way!
- Madam Lee, please!
- You moron!
- Let go, let go!
- Madam Lee, please!
Madam Lee!
Damn!
Oh, my.
Where have you been?
Did someone run you dry?
Dry? Yes, someone ran me dry real good.
A scheming grandfather and
a greedy father. Nothing new!
Maybe it's a good thing
she's not their bloodline.
What are you talking about?
Hey, look.
You know that girl Han
Yi Joo's number, right?
Why would you need that, Mother?
I need to examine her myself.
I want to know who she is.
Grandpa, what's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
It's nothing.
I just feel like I'm not being helpful.
What do you mean?
Just a little while ago, thanks to you...
"Thanks to me"? Don't say that.
You know this. Compared to what I owe you,
it was nothing.
I need to pay you back properly.
What is it that you owe me?
What is it that you're doing this?
Anyway, don't worry about it.
Grandpa will make your
wedding happen somehow.
Yes, thank you, Grandpa.
I'll be back.
Make sure you eat, okay?
I knew it was you.
Why are you following me?
I work for Lee Jung Hye. I
do whatever she tells me to.
No. You're watching me on your own accord.
You saw me meet with my
grandfather last time, too.
But you didn't report to Lee Jung Hye.
So you knew.
Why not?
You work for Lee Jung Hye, Manager Kim.
If Lee Jung Hye is threatened, you
will destroy anyone else in her place.
Tell me.
This behavior, which is unlike you.
How should I interpret that?
Don't decide what "being myself" is for me.
I can change whenever, or however I want.
This is unlike you.
You don't get to decide
what "being myself" is for me.
I can change however I
want, whenever I want.
I liked what you said back then.
Are you wondering who'll win
between Lee Jung Hye and me or...
trying to figure out who to bet on?
Well...
maybe both?
So, you could be on my team.
Let me make an offer. Be on my team.
I'll pay you anything you want.
I don't need money.
Then what do you need?
I'll think about whose
team I want to be on.
At least while I'm trying to figure it out.
Everyone, be careful. It's hot.
And leave it at room
temperature for a moment.
I'll come around and look.
The color should look like this.
No.
What's wrong, Cha Yeon Hwa? Why avoid her?
Let me see yours, Yi Joo.
- What do you think, Teacher?
- Well...
how unique.
What do you think? Do you like cooking?
It's good when I have a lot on my mind.
I don't have to think about anything else.
Like painting?
I put the painting I got
from you in my room.
I love it so much.
Really?
I'm so glad.
The first painting I ever sold.
You must have painted
for a while to get so skilled.
Since I was little.
There wasn't much else
for me to do at home.
Why does she talk so much like
that instead of trying to kiss up to me?
You'll get better at cooking soon, too.
This is done, right?
Yes.
- You'll wrap it up?
- Yes.
- For whom? A boyfriend?
- What?
N-No. I'm going to eat it.
Got it. Wait a minute.
- I'll get you a box.
- Okay.
Mother.
By chance... Is this like...
a piece of art or something?
Art?
It's not that good.
No way. Then, it's just a brownie.
You're clueless, aren't you?
Sorry?
Never mind.
You're going to feed this to my son, right?
Cut off the burnt edges.
Maybe sprinkle some sugar powder on top.
As an artist, you really don't
have any decorating instincts.
Gosh, seriously.
Look at you, helping out your
soon-to-be daughter-in-law.
Hey!
This is just my duty as a human being.
How can I look at food like
this and not do something, huh?
I know, right?
What's going on? You didn't call.
- I'm hungry.
- What?
I just came to eat. Is there anything?
Wait!
Wait right here.
Don't come near. Wait there.
Aigoo!
Whoa...
What is this?
Is it a brick?
I made it.
Han Yi Joo, you did?
Is it a piece of art, then?
Sculpture? Something like that?
It's food. It's a brownie.
F-F-Food?
I'll throw it out. Give it to me.
What are you doing?
It might taste good.
Did I break a tooth?
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
I'll make ramen.
You'll have some, right?
Sit down. I'll do it.
So, there's nothing wrong for real, right?
You didn't even call ahead...
I just wanted to see you.
Okay.
Let's try.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Your servant has tasted it for you.
Please have some.
So...
how about your things?
Is that all? You didn't bring much.
I won't be here long anyway.
What?
I feel like, especially today...
you're so...
drawing a boundary.
- I am.
- What?
I don't need to be
acting when it's just us.
This is a fake marriage, after all.
If it doesn't have to
be fake, what happens?
- What?
- What if I wanted a real marriage?
What would you do?
A real marriage?
- What do you mean?
- You know what I mean...
when a man talks to a woman like this.
He just met you a few days ago. And
now he's proposing, meeting your family...
and having you move in?
The people who know Seo Do Guk would
never believe this. That it's nonsense.
He says he doesn't want to know.
Is that something a man in love would say?
That...
can't be.
It can't be?
Why not?
Because I don't have much time.
How much time do you have?
For Han Yi Joo, how much...
time is left?
A year.
So, what I mean is...
we signed a year-long contract.
In business, a contract is sacred.
So...
please respect...
the boundary between us.
Hello?
Han Yi Joo?
Yes.
Who is this?
This is Seo Jung Wook,
Do Guk's older brother.
I'm sorry I couldn't come
to the family introduction.
I'd like to meet you. Do
you have time tomorrow?
Yes.
That works for me.
How about 9 p.m.?
I'll text you the location.
Oh, right...
I'd prefer that Do Guk
doesn't know about this.
I got it.
All right, then.
Oh, my. Didn't think I'd run into you here.
Is this a coincidence?
No, it's destiny.
You come here when you want to drink alone.
Your room is right upstairs.
You know a lot about me, it seems.
At least more than my sister, right?
I also know a lot more
about men than my sister.
I have to go. I have work.
Are you so not attracted to me that
you can't even spend a night with me?
Well?
More like I don't have feelings for you.
Unni doesn't have feelings for you, either.
She only has eyes for Se Hyeok.
Did you take this yourself?
Does that matter?
What matters is that Se Hyeok has
been going over there without you knowing.
You now know what kind
of girl my sister is, right?
Right. I see it now.
Why you're so obsessed with me.
What?
You just don't want to lose to Han Yi Joo.
She's just a poor orphan with nothing...
She can't be better than you...
but you know she shines brighter than you.
And you can't handle it.
That's why you're
desperate to step all over her.
Isn't that how you feel, Han Yoo Ra?
Seo Do Guk, how can you say that?
I'm warning you for the last time.
Stop here before you get uglier.
I have no intention of
playing your disgusting games.
D-Do Guk, Do Guk...
Is Yoo Ra home?
Yes. A while ago.
Give it to me. I'll take it to her.
Yoo Ra? I'm coming in.
Yoo Ra! Yoo Ra! Yoo Ra!
[Sleeping Pills]
Yoo Ra!
No!
How could you do such a thing?
Don't you know how I raised you?
I gave you the best of everything.
Everyone was jealous of you!
If you raised me so diligently,
you must be disappointed
I turned out like this.
What?
Seo Do Guk told me I'm
not as good as Han Yi Joo.
That it's ugly to see me
be so desperate to beat her.
You told me I'm your real child.
That Han Yi Joo is just fake.
Then why do I have to hear that?
Seo Do Guk dare say those things?
That bastard, I'm going to...
I'm sick of it.
What?
Aren't you?
You can't do anything...
yet it's just all talk, Mom.
Seo Do Guk, Han Yi Joo...
Those two!
Yes, I'm at the cafe.
I'm sorry, but my phone is almost dead.
I think it'll shut off on my way there.
You'll recognize me when you
get here. Feel free to keep it off.
Feel free to keep it off.
See you soon.
What matters is that Se Hyeok has
been going over there without you knowing.
[Seo Jung Wook]
Hey, Do Guk. Did you make
it home all right that time?
Since when do we ask about each other?
I hadn't seen you be
that combative in a while.
I really felt it at the meeting.
That this thing was quite important to you.
Of course. It's my company.
No, not work.
Your marriage.
- What?
- Isn't that why you came running over?
You even got a show of
hands in front of everyone.
"Does anyone have a problem
with my marriage? Nope."
I don't know what you mean.
It made me so curious
about your girlfriend.
What kind of person is she?
How would she react if she
knew who Seo Do Guk really was?
What are you scheming?
Well, first of all, she's pretty.
- What?
- I wonder what she's like when she's mad.
I think she might look
pretty when she cries.
Where are you right now?
I asked where are you?
So, who deposited the funds to Jaeil Group?
It's a business account
in the United Kingdom.
I checked with the international bank
that did the transaction but
can't track the accountholder info.
That means it's a paper
company. Is it Seo Do Guk?
I don't see any illegal financial transactions
for Seo Do Guk, personally or professionally.
I'll look in other directions.
And how about the person
I asked you to look into?
Like you said, he seems very
antagonistic toward Seo Do Guk.
Taeja Group's line of
succession may be shifting.
Taeja Constructions' VP Seo Jung Wook,
previously discussed as the successor,
attempted to exclude H-Terier from the planned
collaboration with the reconstruction project.
Regarding the reason, he...
Maybe...
we could talk to him.
Right.
The most important thing in a
collaboration is sharing the same goal.
He said I would recognize him.
Where is he?
Hyung!
Somebody, please help my brother!
Is anyone out there?
Please save him!
Save him!
Is anyone out there?
Hyung!
Please save my brother!
Please save my brother...
Do Guk?
Han Yi Joo.
Where's Seo Jung Wook?
He told me he'd be
here, but I don't see him.
Were you going to meet me with him?
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
N-No, I just...
I just feel... a little...
a little...
Dizzy.
Do Guk! Are you all right?
It's not fair.
What?
You told me not to cross the line...
but you...
You just... crossed the... line...
Do Guk! Do Guk, wake up!
Do Guk! Do Guk!
Do Guk!
What is this, Seo Do Guk? You
were acting like you were fine.
My brother is still the same.
♫ Now I can see my halo ♫
♫ You can't cover up my mind ♫
♫ Everything in red, and I'm not
going back to who I was before ♫
♫ I can't be hurt no more ♫
[Perfect Marriage Revenge]
Your marriage is at stake.
You kept your life through the loan
games. You want to throw it away now?
Trying to blame me, right?
That's not going to happen.
We'll bet on your older brother.
It's an important time for
us. Let's focus on one thing.
Making our wedding happen.
Hey! If you mess up with Seo
Do Guk, it's a fraud marriage.
I know this illness. The emergency
room can't do anything. I know.
♫ Now I can see my halo ♫